Historical Audiovisual Collection, 1912-2012 (bulk 1945-1996 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 4: Events, 1912-2013; 472 items
  - Celebrations/Dedications, 1912-2013; 144 items
    - Charter Day 1946 (200th Anniversary Celebration), 2009; 66; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Annotated silent movie, capturing the events on Charter Day, 1946, one of the days during which Princeton's Bicentennial was celebrated. The film includes campus scenes, an academic procession, and a football match against Princeton's oldest rival Rutgers.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 4:45.
    - Kick-off Meeting of the $53 Million Campaign, 2009; 124; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Account of the kick-off meeting of the $53 million campaign with speeches of Harold R. Medina '09, James F. Oates Jr., '21 and president Robert Goheen.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 11:56 (reel 2).
    - Kick-off Meeting of the $53 Million Campaign, 2009; 124; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Account of the kick-off meeting of the $53 million campaign with speeches of Harold R. Medina '09, James F. Oates Jr., '21 and president Robert Goheen.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 11:56 (reel 2).
    - Kick-off Meeting of the $53 Million Campaign, 2009; 124; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 196)
      Account of the kick-off meeting of the $53 million campaign with speeches of Harold R. Medina '09, James F. Oates Jr., '21 and president Robert Goheen.. Created by Colorlab. Digital Betacam; Duration: 11:56 (reel 2).
    - Class of 1928 Flour Picture and Commencement, 2009; AR.2001.063; 133; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 3)
      Previously misidentified as "Hibben Inauguration." This silent movie, which includes fragmented and repeated scenes and was probably used during a reunion, captures commencement activities of what is assumed to be the Class of 1928, including a benediction by president John Grier Hibben, the smashing of pipes at Cannon Green, and various P-rade scenes. It includes footage of the Class' freshmen "flour picture," when sophomores would dump flour and water on the freshmen prior to their first class picture on the steps of Whig Hall. The P-rade scenes include footage of a tiger and the class of 1909 with noted alumnus Harold Medina. U-matic; Duration: 6:41.
    - Class of 1928 Flour Picture and Commencement, 2009; 133; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 201)
    - Class of 1928 Flour Picture and Commencement, 2009; 133; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 201)
      Previously misidentified as "Hibben Inauguration." This silent movie, which includes fragmented and repeated scenes and was probably used during a reunion, captures commencement activities of what is assumed to be the Class of 1928, including a benediction by president John Grier Hibben, the smashing of pipes at Cannon Green, and various P-rade scenes. It includes footage of the Class' freshmen "flour picture," when sophomores would dump flour and water on the freshmen prior to their first class picture on the steps of Whig Hall. The P-rade scenes include footage of a tiger and the class of 1909 with noted alumnus Harold Medina. VHS; Duration: 6:41.
    - Class of 1928 Flour Picture and Commencement, 2009; 133; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Previously misidentified as "Hibben Inauguration." This silent movie, which includes fragmented and repeated scenes and was probably used during a reunion, captures commencement activities of what is assumed to be the Class of 1928, including a benediction by president John Grier Hibben, the smashing of pipes at Cannon Green, and various P-rade scenes. It includes footage of the Class' freshmen "flour picture," when sophomores would dump flour and water on the freshmen prior to their first class picture on the steps of Whig Hall. The P-rade scenes include footage of a tiger and the class of 1909 with noted alumnus Harold Medina.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 6:41.
    - Class of 1928 Flour Picture and Commencement, 2009; 133; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Previously misidentified as "Hibben Inauguration." This silent movie, which includes fragmented and repeated scenes and was probably used during a reunion, captures commencement activities of what is assumed to be the Class of 1928, including a benediction by president John Grier Hibben, the smashing of pipes at Cannon Green, and various P-rade scenes. It includes footage of the Class' freshmen "flour picture," when sophomores would dump flour and water on the freshmen prior to their first class picture on the steps of Whig Hall. The P-rade scenes include footage of a tiger and the class of 1909 with noted alumnus Harold Medina.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 6:41.
    - Class of 1928 Flour Picture and Commencement, 2009; 133; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 196)
      Previously misidentified as "Hibben Inauguration." This silent movie, which includes fragmented and repeated scenes and was probably used during a reunion, captures commencement activities of what is assumed to be the Class of 1928, including a benediction by president John Grier Hibben, the smashing of pipes at Cannon Green, and various P-rade scenes. It includes footage of the Class' freshmen "flour picture," when sophomores would dump flour and water on the freshmen prior to their first class picture on the steps of Whig Hall. The P-rade scenes include footage of a tiger and the class of 1909 with noted alumnus Harold Medina.. Created by Colorlab. Digital Betacam; Duration: 6:41.
    - 1996 Commencement - Presidential Address (Clinton) - faculty interviews, 2009; 1274; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      C-TEC broadcast preceding the 249th commencement and address by President Bill Clinton, including interviews with faculty and staff. Clinton's address itself is not captured.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 1:12:22.
    - 1996 Commencement - Presidential Address (Clinton) - faculty interviews, 2009; 1274; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      C-TEC broadcast preceding the 249th commencement and address by President Bill Clinton, including interviews with faculty and staff. Clinton's address itself is not captured.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 1:12:22.
    - Unidentified meal, circa 2009; 56; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 133)
      Footage (black and white, with opening in color) of guest having lunch or dinner on long tables, possibly during bicentennial celebrations. 16 mm; Duration: 2:00.
    - Unidentified meal, circa 2009; 56; 1 Disc(s) (Box 226)
      Footage (black and white, with opening in color) of guest having lunch or dinner on long tables, possibly during bicentennial celebrations. Created by Princeton Media Services. DVD; Duration: 2:00.
    - Princeton Film, including scenes of Princeton Bicentennial Convocation, 2013; 2360; 1 Disc(s) (Box 226)
      A film entitled Princeton written by Irving Jacob \u201931 and Basil Beyer, directed by Alexander Hamid, and produced by Affiliated Film Producers, Inc., and the International Film Foundation, circa 1947. The film has no sound, and appears to have both documentary footage (Princeton Bicentennial Convocation with President Truman, General Eisenhower and Albert Einstein), as well as some scripted scenes. Convocation at approximately 5 minutes 30 seconds. Converted from 16mm film by Princeton Media Services. Created by Princeton Media Services. DVD; Duration: 30 minutes.
    - Tour to West Point, undated; 189; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 164)
    - Princeton -- Hesel Hill Opening, undated; 525; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box DVD)
      Created by Hesel Hill. U-matic.
    - Princeton Hospital, New Leader, undated; AR.2001.010; 1569; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box *missing*)
      Item missing as of 7/18/2011. 16 mm.
    - Prof. Walker Bleakney Retirement, undated; AR.2005.112; 2056; 4 Audio Reel(s) (Box 206)
    - Prof. Walker Bleakney Retirement, undated; AR.2005.112; 2056; 2 Disc(s) (Box 207)
    - Dan Griffin -- Secretary of Alumni Council, 1935 - 1959, undated; 2133; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 203)
      Do not transcibe -- ???? (interviewer produced nothing). Compact cassette.
    - Schultz Dedication, undated; AR.2005.105; 2288; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 215)
  - Documentary/Newsreels, 1928-2012; 225 items
    Subseries contains materials related to entertainment and broadcast spots, documentaries, and newsreels.
    - 1928 home movie footage of Princeton University and Princeton Inn, AR.2007.035; 2200; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
      Low resolution (640x480) video. Transferred from VHS in 2007, original film footage is lost. Created by John Lemaire Libbincott. DVD; Duration: 3:30.
    - 1928 home movie footage of Princeton University and Princeton Inn, AR.2007.084; 2200; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 224)
      Low resolution (640x480) video. Original film footage is lost; copy created 2007. Created by John Lemaire Lippincott. Quicktime-DV; Duration: 3:30.
    - Princeton, 1948; 105; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 147)
      1948 film with post-1951 inserts relating to Forrestal Campus. Created by Martin Bovey Productions. 16 mm.
    - Princeton, 1948; 105; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 223)
      1948 film with post-1951 inserts relating to Forrestal Campus. U-matic.
    - "Too Hot for Toddy" -- Princeton University Traiangle Club, 1950; AR.2004.054; 2180; 2 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 218)
    - "Too Hot for Toddy" -- Princeton University Traiangle Club, 1950; AR.2004.054; 2180; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - WPRB program on death of Albert Einstein, 1955; 742; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 82)
    - WPRB program on death of Albert Einstein, 1955; 742; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
      Created by Princeton Media Services. Compact disc.
    - WPRB program on death of Albert Einstein, 1955; 742; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 203)
    - Woodrow Wilson: Spokesman for Tomorrow, 1956; 93; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 143)
      Hist., Social Science, and Internt'l Relations. Narrorated - mostly as US President, little as Princeton U Pres.. Created by McGraw-Hill Textfilms. 16 mm; Duration: 27 min.
    - Woodrow Wilson: Spokesman for Tomorrow, 1956; 93; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 201)
      Hist., Social Science, and Internt'l Relations. Narrorated - mostly as US President, little as Princeton U Pres. U-matic; Duration: 27 min.
    - Woodrow Wilson: Spokesman for Tomorrow, 1956; 93; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 201)
      Hist., Social Science, and Internt'l Relations. Narrorated - mostly as US President, little as Princeton U Pres. VHS; Duration: 27 min.
    - Princeton Contexts, A Student View, 1962; AR.2014.110; 2387; 1 Disc(s) (Box 233)
      A documentary film by John McKee with text by Jim Bierman. DVD.
    - "Five College Presidents" -- WNDT, 1965; 2194; 4 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
      From Presidents' Records (Goheen). DAT cassette.
    - Episode of Princeton "GE College Bowl" (NBC) Appearance, 1966; AR.2015.003; 2383; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      The College Bowl DVD has 3 videos of Princeton's 1966 "College Bowl" (NBC) loss to Agnes Scott College and the rest of the videos are recordings of a Discovery Channel broadcast (out of scope). DVD.
    - Woodrow Wilson School Freshman Parents, 1970; 612; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 80)
    - Princeton: A Search for Answers, 1973; AR.2001.067; 1466; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 188)
      Recruiting film, produced and directed by Julian Krainin and DeWitt L. Sage Jr. Faculty featured include, among others, Aaron Lemonick (Physics), Edward Cone (Music), John Wheeler (Physics), Daniel Seltzer (English), Ann Douglas Wood (English), and President William G. Bowen. 16 mm; Duration: 30:23.
    - Princeton: A Search for Answers, 1973; 1466; 1 Disc(s) (Box 226)
      Recruiting film, produced and directed by Julian Krainin and DeWitt L. Sage Jr. Faculty featured include, among others, Aaron Lemonick (Physics), Edward Cone (Music), John Wheeler (Physics), Daniel Seltzer (English), Ann Douglas Wood (English), and President William G. Bowen. DVD; Duration: 30:23.
    - Princeton: A Search for Answers, 1973; 1466; 2 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
      Recruiting film, produced and directed by Julian Krainin and DeWitt L. Sage Jr. Faculty featured include, among others, Aaron Lemonick (Physics), Edward Cone (Music), John Wheeler (Physics), Daniel Seltzer (English), Ann Douglas Wood (English), and President William G. Bowen. 2 copies; 1 copy with out-of-sync audio. VHS; Duration: 30:23.
    - Princeton: A Search for Answers, 1973; AR.2002.084; 1466; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 230)
    - Princeton: A Search for Answers, 1973; AR.2004.042; 1466; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 230)
    - Princeton: A Search for Answers, 1973; 1466; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 230)
    - Princeton: A Search for Answers, 1973; Digital Files: 1
      Item number: 1466. Recruiting film, produced and directed by Julian Krainin and DeWitt L. Sage Jr. Faculty featured include, among others, Aaron Lemonick (Physics), Edward Cone (Music), John Wheeler (Physics), Daniel Seltzer (English), Ann Douglas Wood (English), and President William G. Bowen. Duration: 30:23.
    - A Walk in the Springtime (Dr. Fox), 1974; 503; 1 Videotape Reel(s) (Box 220)
      1 inch videotape; Duration: 20 min 30 sec.
    - Two Seniors - edited, 1974; 511; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 13)
    - A Walk in the Springtime - re-edited, 1974; 514; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 14)
      U-matic; Duration: 27 min.
    - A Walk in the Springtime - re-edited, 1974; 516; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 15)
      Film in which Frederic Fox '39, with the help of Sandy Maxwell '39 and Arthur (Buz) Schmidt '74, investigates what has changed and how much is still the same on Princeton campus, less than five years after coeducation was introduced. U-matic; Duration: 20:50.
    - A Walk in the Springtime, 1974; 521; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 16)
      "original". U-matic; Duration: 27 min.
    - A Walk in the Springtime - Two Seniors - re-edited, 1974; 522; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 17)
      U-matic; Duration: 32 min.
    - Two Seniors, 1974; 523; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 17)
    - Two Seniors - re-edited, 1974; 524; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 17)
    - Outtakes of "A Walk in the Springtime", 1974; 528; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      Outtakes of "A Walk in the Springtime," containing discussion about the opening of the film. Compact disc.
    - Dean Ernest Gordon about the Princeton University Chapel, 1977; AR.2000.088; 1974; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 190)
      Film first presented on national television on 11/27/1977 at 9:30 AM\n\n\n\nDean Ernest Gordon describes the windows, carvings, and architectural design of the Princeton University Chapel. Includes elaborate views of the windows.. Created by NBC. 16 mm; Duration: 11:56.
    - Poliodal Divertor Experiment (PDX) -- Princeton Plasma Physics Laboratory, 1978; AR.2006.037; 2116; 1 Disc(s) (Box 209)
      DVD; Duration: 20 min.
    - A Campaign for Princeton, circa 1980; AR.2012.071; 2359; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 232)
      A fundraising film featuring James Henderson '56 and Dean of the Faculty Aaron Lemonick. 16 mm.
    - A Campaign for Princeton, circa 1980; AR.2012.071; 2359; 1 Disc(s) (Box 232)
      A fundraising film featuring James Henderson '56 and Dean of the Faculty Aaron Lemonick. DVD.
    - The Solicitation Process for "A Campaign for Princeton", 1982; AR.1993.031; 51; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 131)
      Instructional video for alumni learning how to do fundraising for "A Campaign for Princeton. 16 mm; Duration: 13:51.
    - Jimmy Stewart - "Tonight Show" with Johnny Carson, 1982; AR.2001.063; 1331; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 26)
    - You Asked For It: An Introduction to Campaign Solicitation, 1982; AR.2001.067; 1422; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 31)
      Created by Carob Video. VHS.
    - Campaign for Princeton, 1982; 1842; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
    - Stocks and Bondage -- 93rd Annual Triangle Show - McCarter Theatre, 1982; AR.2009.013; 1985; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - Stocks and Bondage -- 93rd Annual Triangle Show - Tour, 1982; AR.2009.013; 1986; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
      probably Hunter College in New York City. Compact cassette.
    - Ella Fitzgerald in Concert, 1982; AR.2009.013; 1988; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
      McCarter Theatre. Compact cassette.
    - Tokamak Fusion Test Reactor (TFTR) First Plasma -- Princeton Plasma Physics Laboratory, 1982; AR.2006.037; 2106; 1 Disc(s) (Box 209)
      DVD; Duration: 33 min.
    - Princeton: An Enduring Commitment, 1983; AR.1993.031; 53; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 132)
      Created by Telequest. 16 mm.
    - Under the Influence -- 94th Annual Triangle Show - Reunions Show, 1983; AR.2009.013; 1987; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - '87 Minutes of the Best of Triangle -- 1983 Freshman Week Show, 8pm, AR.2009.013; 1989; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - Under the Influence -- 94th Annual Triangle Show - Act I, 1983; AR.2009.013; 2005; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - The Phil Donohue Show with President A. Bartlett Giamatti, Mr. John Wilhelm Topic: Yale strike/Local 34, 1984; 1946; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 7)
    - Revel Without a Pause -- Princeton University Triangle Club, AR.2009.013; 1984; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - '88 Minutes of the Best of Triangle - 1984 Freshman Week Show, 8pm, AR.2009.013; 1990; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - '88 Minutes of the Best of Triangle - 1984 Freshman Week Show, 8pm and 10:30pm, AR.2009.013; 1991; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
      Composite of both shows, McCarter Theatre. Compact cassette.
    - Revel Without a Pause -- 95th Annual Triangle Show - Saturday Matinee, 1984; AR.2009.013; 1996; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - Revel Without a Pause -- 95th Annual Triangle Show - Sunday Performance, 1984; AR.2009.013; 1997; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - Revel Without a Pause -- 95th Annual Triangle Show - Compilation Tape, 1984; AR.2009.013; 1998; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - Revel Without a Pause - 95th Annual Triangle Show, 1984; AR.2009.013; 1999; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - '88 Minutes of the Best of Triangle - 1984 Freshman Week Show, 10:30pm, AR.2009.013; 2000; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - No. 96 Untitled - 96th Annual Triangle Show, 1985; AR.2009.013; 1992; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - No. 96 Untitled - 96th Annual Triangle Show, 1985; AR.2009.013; 1993; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - No. 96 Untitled - 96th Annual Triangle Show, 1985; AR.2009.013; 1994; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - No. 96 Untitled - 96th Annual Triangle Show, 1985; AR.2009.013; 1995; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 193)
    - Princeton University -- Craft's College Previews, 1985; AR.2002.068; 2130; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 210)
      VHS; Duration: 18 min.
    - Tokamak Fusion Test Reactor (TFTR) Stock Footage, 1986; AR.2006.037; 2107; 1 Disc(s) (Box 209)
      DVD; Duration: 30 min.
    - Firestone Library Staff Training, "On Line Catalogue," Louisa Paster, 1987; 1828; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - Ira's Update on C.I.T. (Computing and Information Technology), Ira Fuchs, 1987; 1870; 4 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - The Tokamak Fusion Test Reactor (TFTR) Story -- Princeton Plasma Physics Laboratory, 1988; AR.2006.037; 2109; 1 Disc(s) (Box 209)
      DVD; Duration: 16 min.
    - The Sun of Man (NJN) -- Princeton Plasma Physics Laboratory, 1989; AR.2006.037; 2104; 1 Disc(s) (Box 209)
      DVD; Duration: 60 min.
    - Documentary in German on America's global position - fourth of five segments on Princeton University, campus idealism/internationalism, circa 1989; AR.2001.067; 1445; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 34)
    - Princeton University: Conversations That Matter, 1991; AR.1994.074; 128; 1 Videotape Reel(s) (Box 220)
      Admission video about life and academics at the university. Footage includes discussion groups, precepts, lectures, and interviews with students and faculty, including Tony Morrison, John Fleming, Peter Brown, and Cornel West.. Created by Andrew Greenspan and Assoc. 1 inch videotape; Duration: 27:24.
    - "Princeton 8/2/1991" - Defining Moments?, AR.2001.063; 1265; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 101)
      Created by Andrew Greenspan and Associates. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
    - "Princeton 8/2/1991" - Defining Moments?, AR.2001.063; 1265; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 128)
      Created by Andrew Greenspan and Associates. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
    - Jeopardy!: Princeton category, 1991; AR.2001.067; 1418; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 31)
      Created by WABC-TV. VHS.
    - "Who Will Teach for America?" - documentary on Teach for America - with Wendy Kopp '89 and Professor Marvin Bressler, 1991; AR.2001.067; 1426; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 32)
    - "The Exile" - in Chinese - exiles at Princeton following 1989 Tiananmen Square protests, 1991; AR.2001.067; 1537; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 42)
    - Princeton University: Conversations That Matter, 1991 September 4; AR.2007.034; 128; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 205)
      Admission video about life and academics at the university. Footage includes discussion groups, precepts, lectures, and interviews with students and faculty, including Tony Morrison, John Fleming, Peter Brown, and Cornel West. Betacam SP; Duration: 27:24.
    - "A Return to Princeton", 1991 September 25; AR.2005.105; 2293; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 216)
      Created by Andrew Greenspan and Associates. VHS; Duration: 15:22.
    - "A Return to Princeton", 1991 September 25; AR.2007.034; 2293; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 205)
      afety Dub of Final Show - Used by Robert Allen and Greenspan to make the Goheen video (item #2025). Betacam SP; Duration: 15:22.
    - Princeton University: Conversations That Matter, 1992; AR.1994.074; 128; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 154)
      Admission video about life and academics at the university. Footage includes discussion groups, precepts, lectures, and interviews with students and faculty, including Tony Morrison, John Fleming, Peter Brown, and Cornel West. 16 mm; Duration: 27:24.
    - Princeton University: Conversations That Matter, 1992; 128; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 201)
      Admission video about life and academics at the university. Footage includes discussion groups, precepts, lectures, and interviews with students and faculty, including Tony Morrison, John Fleming, Peter Brown, and Cornel West. VHS; Duration: 27:24.
    - Princeton University: Conversations That Matter, 1992; AR.1994.074; 128; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 45)
    - Princeton University: Conversations That Matter, 1992; 128; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Admission video about life and academics at the university. Footage includes discussion groups, precepts, lectures, and interviews with students and faculty, including Tony Morrison, John Fleming, Peter Brown, and Cornel West.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 27:24.
    - Princeton University: Conversations That Matter, 1992; 128; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Admission video about life and academics at the university. Footage includes discussion groups, precepts, lectures, and interviews with students and faculty, including Tony Morrison, John Fleming, Peter Brown, and Cornel West.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 27:24.
    - Princeton University: Conversations That Matter, 1992; Digital Files: 1
      Item number: 128. Admission video about life and academics at the university. Footage includes discussion groups, precepts, lectures, and interviews with students and faculty, including Tony Morrison, John Fleming, Peter Brown, and Cornel West. Duration: 27:24.
    - "My Mother's Murder" (documentary about unsolved 1989 murder of Princeton woman Emily Stuart), 1992; AR.2001.067; 1412; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 31)
      Created by Charles C. Stuart. VHS.
    - HBO America Undercover: airing of "My Mother's Murder", 1992; AR.2001.067; 1421; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 31)
      contains other HBO footage. Created by Charles C. Stuart. VHS.
    - MTV's "House of Style" - Raising Women's Voices conference at Princeton: The Power of Beauty, The Beauty of Power, 1993; AR.2001.067; 1449; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 34)
      taped 12/1-5/1992, aired 1/12/1993. VHS.